Guide to the Cornell University Department of Natural Resources records, 1909-1995.
Cornell University Department of Natural Resources records, 1909-1995.
- NREM- Steering Committee, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 49)
- NRES 106, Spring 1988 (Box 27, Folder 50)
- NRES 106-107 (Box 27, Folder 51)
- NRES 106-107, Spring 1989 (Box 27, Folder 52)
- NRES 106-107, Spring 1989 (Box 27, Folder 53)
- NRES 106-107-201-407, Fall 1987-Spring 1988 (Box 27, Folder 54)
- NRES 107, Spring 1988 (Box 27, Folder 55)
- NRES 107- Final Exam, Spring 1988 (Box 27, Folder 56)
- NRES 107- Final Exams, Spring 1989 (Box 27, Folder 57)
- NRES 402- Course Notes, Evaluations, Syllabi, Photos, 1995-1997 (Box 27, Folder 58)
- NRES 402- Course Materials, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 59)
- NRES 402- Course Materials, 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- NRES 402- Course Materials, 2000-2001 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- NRES 493- Course Materials, Handouts, Spring 1987 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- NRES 493- General (I of II), Spring 1987 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- NRES 493- Resource Management in the Northern Yellowstone Ecosystem, 1990-1992 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- NRES- Alumni, Reunions, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- NRES- American Fisheries Society Breakfast, August 25, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- NRES Basic Team- Conference Call, Memos, Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- NRES Base Program Strategic Team Handbook, 2000, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- NRES Christopher M. Klyza Seminar, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- NRES- Correspondence, Notes, Memorabilia, Articles, 1969-2002 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- NRES- DNR 50/100 Celebration, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- NRES Fernow Hall Display, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- NRES- History of Forestry at Cornell, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- NRES Faculty Positions- Memos, Reports, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- NRES 50/100 Celebration- Core Committee Meeting Minutes, Alumni Notes, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- NRES 50 yr. Celebration- Alumni News 1994-1998 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- NRES Screening Committee Emails, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- NRES "S.E. Agents at D. Bruce, June 1965" (photo) (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Long Island Sea Grant- Correspondence, Memos, 1995-1999 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Long Island Sea Grant- Correspondence, 1995-2000 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- NY Sea Grant- Articles, Correspondence, Photo, 1981-1987 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- NY Sea Grant- Correspondence, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- NY Sea Grant Extension Program- Correspondence, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- NY Sea Grant Institute (May 1992)- Status Report, 1987-1991 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- NY Sea Grant Institute- Advisory Service Program, 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- NY Sea Grant Institute- Correspondence, Memos, Tables, Notes, 1974, 1984-1985 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- NY Sea Grant Institute- Correspondence, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- NY Sea Grant- Narratives (Robert Buerger; Ken Gall; Stephen Lopez; Jay Tanski), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- NY Sea Grant- Narratives (Buerger; Dawson; Gall; Greene; O'Neill; Sant'Angelo), 1985 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- NY Sea Grant- Narratives, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- NY Sea Grant- Narratives, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 32)
- NY Sea Grant Program, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- NY Sea Grant Program- Publications, [n.d.] (Box 28, Folder 34)
- Northeastern Association of Fish and Wildlife Agencies- 53rd Annual Conference, April 27-30, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 35)
- Papers by Charles Krueger, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 36)
- Photos, [n.d.] (Box 28, Folder 37)
- Plans of Work, 1964-1968 (Box 28, Folder 38)
- Report of Committee on Program Review, 1986-1999 (Box 28, Folder 39)
- Proceedings: ECOP-PLC- Base Programs, March 29-31, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 40)
- Proposal for Improvement of Enviornmental Natural Resource Curriculum Program, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 41)
- Report of the Task Force on Community Resource Development, April 15, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 42)
- Resource Policy Management/Resource Policy and Human Studies Group (RPM/RPHS)- Meeting, Minutes, [n.d.] (Box 29, Folder 1)
- RPHSG- Newsletter, Representative Publications, 1940- 1995 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- RPHS/RPM Group- Correspondence, Memos, Course Notes NR607, 608, 1992-1997 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- "Running Head: Macroinvertibrate Production in Streams," [n.d.] (Box 29, Folder 4)
- A Rural Development Program for New York State, October 1964 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Status of Staff through 1985 (from 1977), 1982 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Time Savers, 1971- 1997 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Warm Water Pond Meetings, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Wildlife Society Bulletin- Correspondence re: Welch's Papers, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Baer, Jr., Richard A.- Publications, 1966- 1981 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Bell, Wayne T., Jr.- Publications, 1967- 1969 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Brumstead, Harlan B.- Publications, Papers, 1952- 1971 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Brumstead, Harlan B.- Publications, 1951- 1967 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Brumstead, Harlan B.- Publications, 1956- 1969 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Carlson, Clarence A.- Publications, 1965- 1970 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Caslick, James W.- Publications, 1955- 1979 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Conservation in Some Island Areas (Various Authors), 1968- 1969 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Conservation in Some Island Areas (Various Authors), 1968- 1969 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Dawson, Chad P.- Publications, 1979- 1980 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Department of Observation- Publication Research Series, 1967- 1976 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Dickson, Alex- Correspondence, 1968- 1969 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Dickson, Alex- Proceedings: School for Christmas Tree Growers, 1965- 1970 (1966, 1968 missing) (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Dickson, Alex- Proceedings: School for Christmas Tree Growers, 1971, 1972, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Dickson, Alex- Publications, 1960- 1974 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Eipper, Alfred W.- Publications, 1959- 1972 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Everhart, W. Henry- Publications, 1966- 1971 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- Fahey, Timothy J.- Publications- 1981- 1984 (Box 29, Folder 28)
- Fahey, Timothy J.- Publications- 1981- 1984 (Box 29, Folder 29)
- Fazio, James R.- Publications, [1970] (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Fishery Biology Students- Publications, 1961- 1971 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- Flick, William A.- Publications, 1966- 1977 (Box 29, Folder 32)
- Forney, John L.- Publications, 1957- 1971 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Gavin, Thomas, A.- Publications, 1977- 1989 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Gilbert, Douglas L.- Publications, 1956- 1970 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Gillett, James W.- Publications, 1974, [1977] (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Hamilton, Lawrence S.- Publications, 1957- 1965 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Hamilton, Lawrence S.- Publicatiosn, 1954- 1971 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Hamilton, Lawrence S.- Publications, 1954- 1971 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Hamilton, Lawrence S.- Publications, 1954- 1971 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Hamilton, Lawrence S.- Publications, 1954- 1971 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Hardy, Ernest E.- Publications, 1977- 1988 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Harwell, Mark A.- Publications, 1977- 1981 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Hewitt, Oliver H.- Publications, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Kelley, John W.- Publications, 1961- 1978 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Lemons, John- Publications, 1982- 1986 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- McNeil, Richard J.- Publications, Correspondence, 1962- 1969 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- McNeil, Richard J.- Publication: "Population Dynamics and Economic Impact of Deer in Southern Michigan", 1962 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- McNeil, Richard J.- Publication: "In Pursuit of the Universal Oneness", 1974 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Mills, Edward L.- Publications, Papers, 1968- 1971 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Moen, Alfred N.- Publications, Papers, 1968- 1971 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Morrow, Robert R.- Publications, 1953- 1972 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Noble, Richard L.- Publications, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Oglesby, Ray T.- Publications, 1968- 1976 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Oglesby, Ray T.- Publications, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Proceedings: Camground Management Conference, 1968- 1969 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Regier, Henry A.- Publications, 1960- 1968 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Richmond, Milo- Publications, 1969- 1973 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Tate, James Jr.- Publications, 1966- 1970 (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Thompson, Daniel Q.- Publications, 1951- 1967 (Box 30, Folder 28)
- Watson, Jay F.- Publications, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 29)
- Webster, Dwight A.- Publications, 1947- 1977 (Box 30, Folder 30)
- Wilkins, Bruce- Correspondence, 1981- 1986 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Wilkins, Bruce T.- Publications, 1951- 1983 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- Winch, Fred E., Jr.- Publications, 1960- 1975 (Box 30, Folder 32)
- Winch, Fred E., Jr.- Publications, 1960- 1975 (Box 30, Folder 33)
- "The Laws of Conservation" lecture by Kenneth E. Boulding for the Andrew D. White Professors-at-Large Program, Fall 1974 (Box 31)
- "Zooplankton, Zoobenthos and Fish Populations in Canadarago Lake During the Initial Stages of Nutrient Control" by David M. Green and Stephen B. Smith of the Dept. of Natural Resources, March 1976 (Box 31)
- "A Study of Outdoor Recreation Potential and Its Feasibility" for the Waverly, New York Water Supply Impoundments and Watershed- by Mary Anderson, Charlene Aronson, Barbara Askew, Gerallyn Downes, Andrea Holtzman, Cynthia McGraw, January 1979 (Box 31)
- "An Analysis of Its Natural Resources and Multiple Use Management" - Cumming Nature Center - by John W. Kelley, March 1980 (Box 31)
- Cornell Cooperative Extension Programming in Natural Resources - Orientation and Overview, August 1988 (Box 31)
- Publications of the Cornell Biological Field Station, March 1991 (Box 31)
- Annual Report of the Cornell Biological Field Station, 1992-1993 (Box 31)
- Annual Report of the Department of Natural Resources, October 1994-September 1995 (Box 31)
- Department History and Cornell Biological Field Station (Shackelton) - contains many photos, no date (Box 32, Folder 1-4)
- Department Expectations and History, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Natural Resources Committee - New York State College of Agriculture and State University College of Forestry - Public Education Subcommittee, 1966-1968 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Natural Resources Committee, 1962-1965 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Natural Resources Committee - Membership and Subcommittees, 1964-1968 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Natural Resources Committee - Subcommittees, 1964-1967 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Predation and Northeastern Birds of Prey - Extension Education Program, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 10-12)